{
    "id": "8258e5fb1f164cbd8802a8afc0464965",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The actor’s individuality …………………….. him interesting.",
            "description": "We use the simple present tense to talk about facts.",
            "answers": [
                "makes",
                "is making",
                "make"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b717624d10de44c28bf7f4e705a82a3a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Both men were ………………………. inebriated to drive.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c2a762f0d03d4834a0fca41c9cf1e76e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The man was so inert …………………… he seemed dead.",
            "description": "Note the pattern so ..that.",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "for",
                "because"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c5c9b64ba9184efdac42e289c8eadd1c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Blame your inertia ……………………….. the hot weather.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a5fa2ba5faf6432cb402079116a7a714"
        },
        {
            "question": "The crew felt unsafe …………………….. an inexperienced pilot.",
            "description": "We use the preposition with after safe and unsafe.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "by",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dacb7ecefd114d3fb8808ec37d0b2be8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Many men were infatuated ………………………. the beautiful young widow.",
            "description": "We use the preposition with after infatuate. ",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d60d03ba2c4f4c2594f814b16614aea6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Brass is inferior ………………………. gold.",
            "description": "We use the preposition to after inferior and superior.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "than",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "136d408200b84600892efc9bc0ce1e80"
        },
        {
            "question": "The police must inform the prisoner ………………………….. his legal rights.",
            "description": "We use the preposition of after inform.",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "of",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b47c7ad41fee45138a848a22c4ee0337"
        },
        {
            "question": "Information ……………………. witchcraft can be found at the library.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "on",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fb56dc96aae24947856251039abc305d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Children are more …………………………. than adults.",
            "description": "Ingenuous means frank, open and naive.",
            "answers": [
                "ingenuous",
                "ingenious"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ee3777f0afd6413f8a339e0695b80e22"
        },
        {
            "question": "Smart phones are ……………………… devices.",
            "description": "Ingenious means clever or imaginative.",
            "answers": [
                "ingenious",
                "ingenous",
                "ingenuous"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4966e5d2ef064eccb8915cfa7989e38a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mozart had an innate genius ……………………… music.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "74bf9ca709b84852bc0f11bdfa1a1d8f"
        }
    ]
}